SUSAN M. YLARDE





sansumojica@gmail.com () 36 Maen Bin Zaeda Jabbal Amman Jordan () +962-7793-04640



CAREER SUMMARY

Highly motivated Caregiver with solid years of caregiving skills and expertise in helping patients feel secure and understand I'm here available to help them act quickly and adapt to various situations, eager for new challenges. I am a hardworking person with a positive perspective in life and can manage tasks with precision and efficiency. Hardworking & empathetic person with multitasking and time management abilities.

WORK HISTORY

Oct 2019 – present Amman, Jordan

Caregiver, Private Employer - Waseem Alhanbali

Patient Case: Female, 57 years old-cancer patient, severe OCD, stroke

- Help clients with physical therapy exercises
- Address client needs with respect and attention to safety
- · Assist clients with daily living activities, including bathing, grooming, dressing, eating, and using the bathroom
- Help with meal preparation, planning, and grocery shopping
- Monitor vital signs, blood sugar level, oxygen administration, nebulization
- · Provide professional caring client interaction and maintain patients rights to confidentiality while providing excellent costumer service with their families.
- Monitor and record vital signs such as temperature, blood pressure, pulse and respiratory rates.

May 2019 - Sep 2019

Amman, Jordan

Caregiver, Private Employer

Patient Case: Comatose Male Patient, PEG tube, prostate

- · Provide companionship.
- Help clients take prescribed medication.
- Assist clients with ambulation, personal care and hygiene.
- Taking care of patient 85 years old male patient, address needs with respect and attention to safety
- Assist clients with grooming, dressing, eating, and using the bathroom
- Monitor vital signs, blood sugar level, oxygen administration, nebulization

Dec 2016 - Mar 2019

Amman, Jordan

Caregiver, Private Employer - Nazih Salem Al Mauge & Hannan Al Mauge

- Help clients take prescribed medication.
- Assist clients with ambulation, personal care and hygiene.
- Planning and supervising rest, bed and nap times
- Help with meal preparation, planning, and grocery shopping
- Monitor vital signs, blood sugar level, oxygen administration, nebulization
- Taking care of 93 yrs old female dementia patient
- Taking care patient, address needs with respect and attention to safety

Jun 2012 – Jun 2013

Dasmariñas Cavite, Philippines

Pharmacy Assistant, Ibias Drugstore and Medical Clinic

- Label medication in bottles, tablets or other formats.
- Manage orders from customers.
- Restocking shelves with medications and other pharmaceutical supplies.
- Operate cash register and manage payments.
- Provide advice to customers about non-prescription items.
- Provide medicines on prescription.
- Ensuring that work areas are organized and clean.

SKILLS

- Strong Work Ethic
- · Wellness and illness care
- Compassionate & basic child and adult care
- · Able to work in a flexible environment
- Meal planning and preparation
- Patience and empathy
- Flexibility and commitment
- Excellent customer service
- Vital signs monitoring
- · Direct patient care
- Team player & time management
- · Ability to multitask and adaptability

CERTIFICATES & TRAININGS

National Certificate II in Caregiving TESDA Philippines

Certificate of Completion on Tatak - TQC **CEPPHA Program**

DSAP - Drugstore Association of The Philippines - DKT Health

Certificate of Completion on Labor Management - March 26, 2015 DSAP - Drugstore Association of The Philippines in cooperation with SYDENHAM Pharmaceutical Inc.

EDUCATION

2008 - 2009Dasmariñas Cavite, Philippines

Professional Caregiving Course, AMA Computer College

1991 - 1993Manila, Philippines Pharmacy Aide, Emilio Aguinaldo College